{
    "question": [
        {
            "id": "1",
            "question": "Which state assembly recently passed a resolution to abolish the stateâ€™s legislative council?",
            "options": [
                "Telangana",
                "Maharashtra",
                "Andhra Pradesh",
                "Karnataka"
            ],
            "answer": "Andhra Pradesh"
        },
        {
            "id": "2",
            "question": "Which state government recently approved Ground water Act, 2020, to improve groundwater level?",
            "options": [
                "Bihar",
                "Uttar Pradesh",
                "Jharkhand",
                "Rajasthan"
            ],
            "answer": "Uttar Pradesh"
        },
        {
            "id": "3",
            "question": "Which is the largest Cave in India ?",
            "options": [
                "Ajanta Caves",
                "Amarnath Cave",
                "Borra Caves",
                "Undavalli Cave"
            ],
            "answer": "Amarnath Cave"
        },
        {
            "id": "4",
            "question": "Which is the largest Artificial Lake in India ?",
            "options": [
                "Govind Sagar Lake, Bakra Nangal",
                "Himayat Sagar, Telangana",
                "Rabindra Sarobar, West Bengal",
                "Barua Sagar Tal, Uttar Pradesh"
            ],
            "answer": "Govind Sagar Lake, Bakra Nangal"
        },
        {
            "id": "5",
            "question": "Which is the largest Zoo in India ?",
            "options": [
                "Bannerghatta National Park, Bengaluru, Karnataka",
                "Jaipur Zoo, Rajasthan",
                "Zoological Garden, Kolkata",
                "Nehru Zoological Park, New Delhi"
            ],
            "answer": "Zoological Garden, Kolkata"
        },
        {
            "id": "6",
            "question": "Which is the largest Public Sector Bank in India ?",
            "options": [
                "Industrial Bank of India",
                "Reserve Bank of India",
                "Allahabad Bank of India",
                "State Bank of India"
            ],
            "answer": "State Bank of India"
        },
        {
            "id": "7",
            "question": "Which is the largest Desert in India ?",
            "options": [
                "Kutch, Gujarat",
                "Thar Desert, Rajasthan",
                "Jaisalmer, Rajasthan",
                "Spiti Desert, Himachal Pradesh"
            ],
            "answer": "Thar Desert, Rajasthan"
        },
        {
            "id": "8",
            "question": "The Central Rice Research Station is situated in?",
            "options": [
                "Chennai",
                "Cuttack",
                "bangalore",
                "Hyderabad"
            ],
            "answer": "Cuttack"
        },
        {
            "id": "9",
            "question": "The country that has the highest in Barley Production?",
            "options": [
                "China",
                "India",
                "Russia",
                "France"
            ],
            "answer": "Russia"
        },
        {
            "id": "10",
            "question": "The hottest planet in the solar system?",
            "options": [
                "Mercury",
                "Venus",
                "Mars",
                "Jupiter"
            ],
            "answer": "Venus"
        }
    ]
}